[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 16]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Author: Shan Gu Jun]
Don't look so sad.
Give me a smile.
Look.
I'm perfectly fine.
I'm sorry.
Today,
I caused you trouble again.
I don't mind trouble at all,
especially when it's you.
Have you been
feeling better lately?
Did you see him?
He's there again.
Sometimes,
he stands there looking at me.
Sometimes he wants to rush over.
Sometimes he wants to jump off
like my dad did.
Sometimes...
Is it because of her today?
I want to check on my mom.
Okay.
Let's go together.
Mom.
Tinglan, you're here.
It's been a long time.
Zhuo, you're here too.
Oh, your hand got hurt?
Mom.
I fell accidentally.
Auntie, how are you feeling these days?
Not bad.
Oh, Tinglan,
are you too busy with work?
You've lost weight.
Auntie,
I failed to look after her.
Mom,
has she been here lately?
No.
Sounds good.
Does she make things hard for you at work?
So what if she does?
I couldn't care less.
Let's focus
on making a good life for ourselves.
That's more like it.
I'll focus on getting better too.
I'm waiting for you to take me home.
Oh,
I heated up some food in the microwave.
Go get it for me.
Here.
Have a seat.
If I remember correctly,
you are a client
of Tinglan's company, right?
Yes, Auntie.
Now I get it.
Well…
what do you mean?
Jian's been used
to fighting for things since childhood.
Anything Tinglan likes
or anyone she loves,
she must grab tightly
in her own hands.
Now,
she's out of tricks
to change your mind.
So she has no choice
but to use me instead.
Okay, I got it.
Thanks for your help lately.
[No piling]
Tinglan,
cut the "thanks" every time.
You know what I expect from you?
I know.
But between us,
there are still unresolved issues.
It's been a mess in my place,
so I won't invite you in.
It's okay.
You kept hearing strange noises
from the doorbell?
I'll stand by at the door.
Where is your furniture?
There was too much stuff here.
All those blind spots
have scared me.
Has it gotten this serious?
It's fine.
I'll get some good rest.
You may go.
Tinglan,
how can I feel relieved?
I'm begging you,
can I stay here for the night?
So when those noises appear again,
I can step in immediately.
Suit yourself.
Stop.
Sorry.
Still can't sleep?
Yeah.
But I feel a bit safer
than being home alone.
I'm sorry.
If I had known you were suffering so much,
I would’ve come back earlier.
I went abroad
to...
arrange the work
for the technical department.
It's okay.
You don't have to
avoid her name like that.
She means nothing to me now.
Yeah.
I went abroad
to arrange her work.
She'll spend most of her time abroad
in the future.
Thank you.
However,
let's focus on work for now.
Right now,
I can't cut off all ties with her.
But I promise
that I will put an end
to all personal contact with her.
Jian's been used
to fighting for things since childhood.
We were neighbors.
It was just kids playing around.
Something happened to my family back then.
Sometimes I wanted
to jump off the building
like my dad did.
Yu'an.
Without Jane here,
we can't access the data.
I have the key.
Yu'an,
that's a client's privacy.
We can't access it without reporting it.
Do you know how much damage
it will cause to our company?
Yu'an,
when we founded this company,
our core competitive edge was
ensuring user data security.
Once you access
private user data,
our company's image
will be ruined.
Where is Wen Jian?
Wen Jian?
She went back to headquarters yesterday.
What's wrong?
Tell her
to return immediately.
Yu'an,
what happened?
Sorry.
I don't want anyone else
to know about this.
Weren't you taking us home?
Why are we at your place?
You really want your mom
to see an empty house like yours?
Don't worry.
I won't say anything.
Auntie,
we've arrived.
Let me help you out.
Tinglan,
open the door.
You rented this place.
Who are you waiting for?
Take care.
Tinglan, when did you rent this new place?
You didn't even tell me.
It's close to the company
and more convenient for commuting.
Go on chatting.
I'll go buy some groceries.
Mom,
have a seat.
I've been in the hospital forever.
I've forgotten
what home looks like.
I talked to the doctor.
He said you're doing much better.
Coming home for a few days every week
is better for your recovery.
Our old place
is getting new furniture,
so we brought you here.
Zhuo helped you with this, right?
How long have you been dating?
Mom,
we're not dating.
We're just friends.
I'm clear-headed now.
You'd better
be honest with me.
On New Year's Eve,
he even kept us company in the hospital.
His hand injury I saw
was because of you, right?
And today,
all the way here,
he helped out without complaining.
What kind of ordinary friend
would do so much for you?
Tinglan, tell me the truth.
You like Zhuo too, don't you?